WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
Meadow, do you
have a tampon?
I'm spotting and the
dispenser in the
ladies room is out.
You had an
examination?
I don't know
what's happening.
This is the middle of
the month, this never
happens to me.
Here.
Imagine having
your portrait in a
museum like this.
She's just the
wife of some rich
merchant, mom.
That's how rubens
made his money.
You sure talk the talk
,"miss art history".
I have never seen grades
like this from you.
Well, you take
intro to semiotics.
If you spent more
time in your books
and less in
jackie's car...
please...
that is so over.
Just like that?
What happened?
Are you crying?
What's the matter?
I don't know,
just look at it.
Jusepe de ribera.
"The mystical marriage
of st. Catherine."
That's the baby jesus.
She's marrying a
baby? Good luck.
We all do.
What?
I shouldn't
be sarcastic.
Just look at her
with the little baby's
hand against her cheek.
She's so at peace.
That beautiful,
innocent,
gorgeous little baby.
C'mon, let's
go eat.
Tony?
Oh, tony, c'mon.
I'm sorry about wh
at happened, you won't
return my phone calls.
Go fuck yourself!
Tony...
we have something
too special to just--
over one argument.
One argument?
You threw
a fuckin' dinner
at my head, gloria.
If you were a guy,
i don't have to tell you
where you'd be right now.
You were late!
You kept me waiting
three hours--
what about
the present?
You take a
nice thought,
a nice present,
you throw it out the window
in the fuckin' barnegat bay.
Alright...
i'm having a reall
y bad couple of weeks.
Shit with my family
and other crap...
i was trying t
o act all in control
and not dwell on it.
It's no
excuse, but...
so, what, you can't
talk to me about
your problems?
I didn't want to
bother you with it.
Well, i had a
lot on my plate.
Can i see
you later?
I'm late for my
appointment.
Me and this broad,
we're like
leather and lace,
a burn
ing ring of fire.
Whatever the fuck.
Amour fou...
as the french call it.
Crazy love,
all consuming.
That's it.
I tell ya, we push
each other's buttons.
Most people don't
push your buttons.
That's not true.
I know you think
i'm like a hard, cold,
captain of
industry- type.
That's not
all there is.
I don't know.
She gets freaky.
What do you think?
Is she a full blown
looptiloo or what?
As you well know,
i cannot--
discuss
another patient.
What if i duck you
an extra five?
I'm not charging you
at all this month
because last month
you overpaid.
You gave me a lot of
good tips that session.
I won't have it,
don't offer it again.
Alright, alright,
jesus.
Let's get back
to gloria.
She never wants
any money neither.
And you like
this about her?
She's, you know ve
ry independent- minded.
That i do like.
You see her as
independent, strong.
Why? She's not?
We're talking about
your perceptions.
She made her own
way in the world.
Irina was such a
helpless fuckin' baby.
And gloria
knows a lot,
about a lot of shit.
Buddhism,
and the movies.
She went to morocco
all by herself.
And those eyes...
those dark,
black eyes.
When she stares at
you it's like...
like a spanish princess
in one of those paintings,
a goyim.
Those eyes are deep.
Complicated.
I said deep, you
said complicated.
You said dark.
Spit it out.
Whenever i bring her u
p you get this weird puss.
And then you ask me,
"does she seem happy?"
Like maybe she's not.
Or,"does she remind
you of somebody?"
With that
weird puss on.
Like you don't like
it, our mo- fo,
or whatever the fuck
you call our relationship!
You've told me what
you see in gloria.
What do you think
she sees in you?
Oh, please, huh?
What does
she see in me?
I don't know,
with all the fuckin' faggo
and crybabies running around,
whatever else
i am, i'm not...
i'm more of a...
you know
, like i said,
a captain of
industry- type.
You're a tough guy.
Ah, c'mon.
It's okay,
you can say it.
C'mon, you embarrass m
e with that shit now.
Does gloria know what
you do for a living?
You mentioned fire.
Can we say that there are
certain kinds of people
that are
drawn to fire?
Looking for an
inevitable result?
Like a moth
to a flame?
And this is gloria?
And i'm the flame?
Why would anybody hit
you, of all people,
with a side of beef?
She's complicated.
I said complicated.
Dark, you said.
I said her
eyes are dark.
Nice.
Not bad.
Since we're
kicking up,
we were hoping you
could, you know,
watch our back?
350 buys you
a hello.
Watching
your back,
that's
gonna
require
a little more
initiative on
your part.
Oh, look at the face.
What's he got to
be frowning about?
Tell me, romeo,
now that you
moved back home,
are you gonna
be humpin'
tony soprano's
little girl
on our couch?
Fuck her.
Tony too, with
his "stay in
school" bullshit.
He could've reached ou
t to somebody at rutgers.
He should break
the dean's legs
'cause you're too lazy
to read a fuckin' book.
Now go ahead,
i gotta make
some calls.
You did good.
Keep coming by...
go, go!
I knew a moroccan
guy once.
Hit and ran me,
i tracked him down.
I never
forget a fez.
Jesus christ.
That's the oldes
t joke in the book.
Jesus christ.
Hello?
No, you have
the wrong number.
What?
I thought it
might be my sister.
That family shit you
were telling me about?
Yeah.
It's okay if you don
't want to talk about it.
Really.
She said i can never see
my niece and nephew again.
Right before
christmas.
We had a new santa claus
at our christmas party
in the neighborhood.
He wasn't very good.
I love those two
children so much.
She said i was turning
them against their
father, which i wasn't.
Not that he doesn't
deserve it,
fucking crackhead
sack of shit.
Hannah and seamus
go to this
like, alternative
private elementary school
in santa monica.
Where it's all about the
childrens' self esteem.
I hate that shit.
So, i happened to ask hannah,
she's in the third grade,
"are you gonna be in
the christmas play?"
And she says,
"we don't call it
the christmas play,
we call it the
winter festival."
So i go,"whatever,"
i don't say anything.
And then seamus says,
"we're not allowed
to say christmas,
we call christmas
"the c word."
And i fuckin'
flipped out.
What did seamus say?
The fuck does he
know, he's 10.
So my sister gets
all pissed off
because her husband,
their father,
teaches at the school.
Except for he's on
medical leave for
substance abuse treatment.
And one thing
led to another
and she said i always
had it in for john.
And she forbid me to
ever see them again.
He smokes crack,
this fuck?
Without those
two kids...
maybe we'll
all get lucky.
The way these trucks
go by out here,
maybe i'll
get plastered
onto a grill.
Hey, what the fuck?
I'm just kidding
, it never rains.
I think they're go
nna fire me over at globe.
Fucking arnie mills
sexually harasses me
and then
dares me to sue.
Mm- hmm.
Anyway,
fuck'em.
You like this song?
It's okay.
I love this song.
Guys, if you're gonna
smoke, take it outside.
Fuck's the
matter, you don't
speak english?
Who the fuck
are you?
The owner's a dear
friend of ours.
That should be
enough for you.
Fuck him, too.
What'd you
fuckin' say?
Chill, chill,
relax!
Jackie,
what are
you doin'?
It's alright,
it's under control.
Go find a fuckin' taco bell
before i cap your asses.
Get the fuck
outta here.
Oh, shit, here,
take this.
Fuck no, bro
, he's a made guy.
He's gonna
flip when he
sees this shit.
Roy's his
aunt's cousin.
What's up?
Hey, chris.
The fuck happened?
Ask your
buddy here.
These spics came in, you know,
disrespecting the place.
So, i had to
straighten them out.
You had to
straighten the
m out, how many?
Three.
Goddamn fuckin
' craziness.
You alright, roy?
20 years, i'm collecting
these things.
What the fuck,
it's only glass.
Have a seat.
So, how's business
, you making money?
We're doing alright,
why, you got something?
My favorite,
a truck.
Cigarettes.
Sounds good.
But we're kinda
with ralphie now.
Besides, wouldn't tony
go fuckin' ballistic
if i was in on it?
Hey, unless they're
paying your nut,
nobody has a right
to tell anybody else
how to earn a
fuckin' living.
Finally,
thank you.
Ralphie, huh?
Well, if you
ever think about
jumpin' ship,
you know
my number.
I need the paperwork
on the preowned c- five.
Mrs. Soprano?
Yes.
The courtesy van's
stuck in traffic.
It should only be
maybe 20 minutes.
Oh, well,
maybe i'll just
call a cab.
That's okay, jerry,
i'll give her a lift.
I'm going
out anyway.
Gloria trillo.
Carmela soprano,
you're sure you
don't mind?
Gimme a minute, let
me just grab a demo.
This is very
sweet of you.
Don't believeit.
Everybody's
a potential sale.
So, what do you do?
I'm a homemaker.
Oh.
You must mak
e a very nice home
to drive a benz.
So, you're married.
Yes.
Kids?
Two.
You?
No, to both.
Boys, girls?
One boy, one girl.
The boy's still
in high school
and my daughter's
in college.
She's not too
far away though.
She's in
new york city.
She's at columbia,
actually.
School of broadcasting?
No, no,
the university.
It's in the ivy league,
it's one of the top schools.
I know, i was
just kidding.
Oh.
Right.
These kids today...
they got the world
by the you know what.
Yeah, tell
me about it.
At least your daughter
doesn't have to latch on
to a man for success.
Thank god.
That's a beautiful ring.
Thank you.
What does your
husband do?
Well, he's involved
in a few businesses.
Sounds mysterious.
No, no, it's
not really.
My daughter calls
us bourgeois.
Well, thank you
so much, really.
Oh, it was
no problem.
It was very nice
to meet you.
You too.
Nice house.
Thank you.
I'll tell you,
the thing i like
about moltisanti?
He'll even tell
tony soprano to
go fuck himself.
The guy's fearless.
Who's fearless?
Nobody, chris
moltisanti.
Where's my mother?
She's an
early riser.
What about
moltisanti?
Nothing, we were
just saying he's
young to be made,
that kinda shit.
He wanted it,
so he stepped up
and took it.
It's like your old man
and tony soprano.
How do you think they got
their name on the marquee?
How?
We got any
marshmallows?
C'mon, what about
my father?
When we was kids we
had our own little crew,
me, your dad,
buon anima,
tony, silvio dante.
We'd do mickey
mouse scores,
moving pot...
swag, bullshit stuff.
We thought we were like
the sixth family.
But who the fuck knew
we was even alive, right?
Till one fuckin' night,
and i gotta give your
father credit for this.
He had balls
as big as an irish
broad's ass.
There was this old...
old mustache named...
feech lamanna.
Now, what the hell "feech"
meant who the fuck knows,
but, he was made
on the other side,
so you know, he
was an original.
He was an o. G.
Whatever.
He had this saturday
night card game.
Your father sees this
as our big chance
to step up to
the "a" league.
Connected or not,
him, me, and tony
were gonna rob it.
We thought your father
lost a marble,
but he said,
"fuck it".
Balls.
What happened?
They took it down,
they walked away
with like 20 large.
Jesus christ.
What do you
mean "they"?
You didn't go?
Please...
i'm still
sick over it.
I caught the clap from some
hippie broad i was fuckin'.
My dick was dripping
like a busted pipe.
Anyways, the
rest is history.
Your father and tony was on
the fast track to being made
and i
was still a little shit
heel like the two of you.
Then of course,
i, whatever,
but that was a
few years later.
Did they get
away with it?
What could feech do?
There was a sit- down
and the right people got
some of their money back...
but, the point
was made.
Your father and tony
were rising stars
that had to be respected.
Cocksuckers.
Alright, kiddies,
that's enough
for tonight.
Oh, jackie,
make sure you rinse those
plates before you put them
in the dishwasher.
It clogs.
We can't help but be amazed
at the instincts
they possess...
to protect all
manner of livestock,
to be protective of us.
What can we do
to protect them?
Nurture the defenses
they were born with
using the natural body
defense system in pedigree.
What is wrong
with me?
Pedigree...
hi, there.
Are you drunk?
How'bou
t right here?
You would,
wouldn't you, huh?
Does my car
look slanted?
Oh, shit.
If i have a flat.
Oh, my god.
Jesus christ.
So creepy.
Why?
I don't know.
What?
You know
who did this,
don't you?
The fuck you
talking about?
I saw that look.
The least you coul
d do is not lie to me.
What do i know about
your friggin' tires?
Fine.
Thanks for
your help.
Alright.
One time,
my ex- girlfriend
, she, you know,
got a little jealous
and she slashed my tires.
And that thought went throug
my mind briefly just then.
But it couldn'
t have been her.
Who, the cunt that
called the boat?
Stata zit'
with that.
Stata zit', my
car is fucked!
You work for
a dealership.
What do you think,
i get new free
fucking tires?
So, i'll pay
for it, what's the
big fuckin' deal?
Alright, now, why would
you offer to pay for them
if you didn't
have a guilty
fuckin' conscience?
About what?
Well, i don't know,
you tell me.
This is fucking
bullshit.
I'm going home.
Oh, yeah? Who
else would do it?
Who knows,
kids maybe.
Ruin a great
fuckin' evenin
g over this shit!
Kids?
I don't know,
maybe your fucking
brother- in- law.
Maybe mr. Globe
down at globe motors,
since you're america's
fuckin' sweetheart
this week.
Oh, where the fuck
do you get off?
This immigrant,
alcoholic,
fuckin' probably
hiv- laden slut...!
Slashes my tires
and you have
the fuckin' nerve
to call my life
into question?
She wouldn't do it!
I slapped the piss
out of her last time!
Oh...
did you?
Did you really
hit her?
Alright, look...
she's a poor,
confused kid
from an
underdeveloped
country,
even if she
did do this...
i'll make
a couple of calls,
i'll have two brand new
michelins here in an hour.
What are these,
85 r- 16s,
what?
Jesus christ.
17s!
Gene pontecorvo's
got a card game,
we can take it
down right now.
What are you
fuckin' crazy?
He's with ralph.
So, for all
intents and purposes,
that's ralph's game.
That's even better.
Fuck him and
his "rinse your
dishes" bullshit.
You know what?
I think he's a
fuckin' secret fag.
I don't know, jackie.
Maybe we take carlo too,
he's got a shotgun.
We wear masks,
we go in,
we're out in like
two minutes.
What if they find
out that it's us?
We want them to.
Not right away, but,
you know, like ralph said.
And even when they do, you
know it's gonna get squashed.
My old man was
jackie aprile.
The worse that'll happen,
we have to give
some of it back.
We pull this off,
we're like free agents.
We dictate the
terms, not them.
'Cause we
show balls.
Go on,
call carlo.
Fuck.
There's no signal.
I'd have to be pretty stup
to write a book about killing
and then kill somebo
dy the way i described...
use that phone.
Oh yeah,
this one.
C'mon, hurry up,
call carlo.
They show
my favorite
part yet?
No, i thin
k it's coming up.
The answer's no.
I didn't kill him.
C'mon, move over
, gimme me some room.
Fuck you,
it's my house.
Here it comes.
Yeah!
Would you like a
cigarette, nick?
You two know
each other?
No.
I went to see a
psychiatrist, father.
The that's why father
intintola suggested
i talk to you.
He said that
you were getting
a doctorate in
psychiatry fro
m seton hall.
Psychology.
The psychiatrist told me
that my whole life is a lie
and he's right.
And now i thin
k i'm sick...
and if i die, i will never
be with god in eternity.
You're ill?
I'm pretty sure
i have ovarian cancer.
What does your
doctor say?
I haven't seen one.
I'm afraid.
Why do you think
you're ill?
I'm spotting,
and lower back pain.
My hormones ar
e all over the place.
My cousin kathy
died from it.
God doesn't
punish people
for mistakes
they've made.
He loves you more
than you know.
Have you thought that
with your symptoms
you might be
carrying a child?
I know,
that's another--
would you be
more comfortable
if we set the sacrament
aside for a moment
and stepped
into my office?
The psychiatrist said th
at i should leave my husband.
May god forgive me
, when he said tha
t it seemed so right.
You made a sacred vow.
Divorce is out
of the question.
Unless...
is he abusive,
your husband?
Not to me, but
he is unfaithful.
He's a good man
basically, but...
i talked to father intintola
about all this years ago
and here
i still am.
Do you love
your husband?
I do.
I love my husband
and i love god.
But, my life i
s financed by crime...
his crime.
$50, 000 to my
daughter's college.
The psychiatrist say
s it's all blood money.
And now to maybe bring
another child into this?
God understands
that we all live in
the middle of tensions.
You say your husband
has good in him.
What you have to do
is learn to live on
what the good part earns.
The what?
There's a point
inside yourself,
an inner boundary
beyond which
you feel culpable.
You've got to come
to an awareness
of where that line is
and forego those things
which lay without it.
The church has
changed so much.
It's a complex world.
Learn to live on
the good part.
Forego those things
that lay without it.
I think i can
do that, father.
I'll try.
And go see
an ob- gyn.
This mad cow disease.
I think it's terrible
the english government
didn't tell people sooner.
Maybe they didn't want
to create a stampede.
Oh, by the way,
guess which former
medical student
is no longer datin
g the queen of mean?
You're kidding.
Jackie jr. And meadow
are finished?
Frankly, i
am delighted.
Angie bonpensiero said
that kevin told her
that jackie wa
s smoking marijuana
and he was caught cheating
on an exam at rutgers.
Gee, that bad?
She would've been better
off with that black kid.
He's got a 4. 0
and he's moving
to india for the u. N.
I told you.
She wasted three months
with jackie jr.
Hello.
Mrs. Soprano?
Gloria trillo,
globe motors.
Oh, hi, of course,
how are you?
I hope i'm not calling
you at a bad time.
But the new e- 320
just came in
and i thought you might
want to take a look at it.
Oh, no, i don't th
ink so, thank you though.
I still have
another year
on my lease.
Run it by your husband,
maybe he'll wanna treat you.
Okay, maybe i will.
Thank yo
u for calling.
Okay, bye.
Hope to see ya.
Buh- bye.
What a nice woman.
Who?
Just some saleswom
an from globe motors.
What?
She wants me to test drive
the new e- series wagon.
And i'm not
interested,
but she was awfully
nice to me the other day.
She gave me a
ride home while th
ey serviced the wagon.
But i really should
hold onto it for anoth
er year, don't you think?
Another year...
yeah.
I was just wondering
if we could
switch days off.
Just give me a minute,
could you, martin?
I just thought--
yeah, yeah, sure,
i just got a custo
mer coming in, alright?
Tony.
Don't you fuckin'
"tony" me.
Are you out of your fucking
mind talking to my wife?
I was upset about your
ex- girlfriend, alright?
"Poor, confused kid",
i thought you should
see my version.
I'm sorry,
alright?
You drove her home.
What the fuck?
Then you look right
into my eyes and
you don't tell me?
Alright, it's
just normal
to be curious abou
t someone that you love's
significant others.
No, it's not, it's
fuckin' twisted.
No, it is not.
Look, i don't wa
nt to argue with you.
You're upset
, and i understand
it's on the margin
s for someone like you
and i'm sorry and it'll
never happen again, ever.
No shit.
Now you can tell
your shrink you ruined
eight relationships.
What do you mean?
It's fucking over.
Tony!
You see, tuesday
i can take my
kid to hear raffi.
Left ovary....
right ovary.
Just tell me right
out, dr. Rotelli.
Don't mince words.
I really did not
feel comfortable
with everybody
knowing my personal life.
Where's this
asshole now?
What'd he have,
like one song?
What are you doing?
We should be out
doing what we gotta do.
Call carlo, tell him
to bring his shit.
Who the fuck was
feech lamanna anyways?
You know what?
Don't come.
You want to spend
the rest of your life
with your head up your ass,
be my guest.
How's your
calimar' salad?
I don't think he's using
the right olive oil.
You haven't said
two words, carmela.
I'm sorry.
I just came from
dr. Rotelli's.
Oh, my god, is
everything alright?
Apparently i've
never been better.
Just a lit
tle thyroid thing.
Thank god.
I thought i
was pregnant.
Bite your tongue!
At our age?
I don't know,
with the kids
growing up
and everything.
What i'd give to
have a grandchild.
Terry and her husband
are trying again, but...
speaking of grandkids
i am just sick about
jackie and meadow.
I asked him
what happened,
he tells me to mind
my own business.
So does she in
so many words.
They broke up?
Is meadow okay?
Oh, please, that
girl is so differe
nt than i was at her age.
It just rolls
off her back.
There's no weight loss,
no sleepless nights.
Not like the grief we go
through with our husbands.
That's'cause we married
these walyos.
It's not just us.
The president
of the united states,
for crying out loud.
Look what his wife
had to put up with,
with the blow jobs
and the stained dress.
Hillary clinton?
I can't stand
that woman.
I don't know.
Maybe we could
all take a page
from her book.
What, to be
humiliated in public
and then walk around
smiling all the time?
That is so false.
I would dig a hole,
i would climb into it
and i would
not come out.
All i know is,
she stuck by him
and put up with
the bullshit,
and in the end,
what did she do?
She set up her
own little thing.
She did.
She took all that
negative shit he gaveher
and spun it
into gold.
You gotta
give her credit.
That's true,
isn't it?
She's a role model
for all of us.
The case is
still pending.
They could try me on a
simple mail and wire fraud
but they're holding out,
they'd rather fold i
t into a major rico.
Tony,
line two.
Who is it?
I don't know,
it's a woman.
I think
she's crying.
Let me get
back to you.
Hello?
Tony?
I don't know...
i don't know...
i can't understand you.
I don't know what
you're trying to say.
I can't take
it anymore.
...stay...
i don't know why...
tony...
tony.
Thanks for coming.
Alright.
You want
something to drink?
No.
I'm sorry.
There's no one else
i can talk to.
What about him?
Laugh if you want,
he does help.
Yeah, he's a regular
captain marvel.
I just want it to
be the way it was.
I love you.
Stop it,
gloria.
I'm sorry,
i'm sorry.
Quit fuckin' crying,
i can't stand it.
I want to be
with you.
Well, that's not
gonna happen.
I know.
My life's a
trip to nowhere.
You bring it
on yourself.
You're a beautiful,
talented woman...
but...
you push a man away.
It's not gonna
happen again.
The other night
with the tires,
i'm a grown man.
I've had other women.
You think i
lived in a freezer
before i met you?
Fine.
I'll sit back
like a mute
while you screw
every woman out there.
See, there's
that tone again.
Look...
it's over.
We had our
amour fou
or whatever.
And it was great.
And now it's t
ime to put it to bed.
What'd you think
that you could treat me
like some stupid fucking
goombah housewife?
You think i'm gonna
let some fucker
shit all over me
just'cause he buys me
some ridiculous
gaudy fucking ring?
Where the fuck
do you get off?
You don't care.
You think you're the
only one with problems?
You think my life's
a fuckin' picnic?
Oh, poor you.
You got a fuckin' dream
life compared to mine.
Nobody cares if
i'm alive or dead!
I didn't
just meet you.
I've known you my
whole fuckin' life.
That's right.
Take a dump wherever
you please and then
just walk away.
My mother was
just like you.
Bottomless
black hole.
Oh, the mother now.
I surrender.
Burn me at
the stake.
You know what?
You're fuckin' crazy.
All i ever asked
for was kindness.
C'mere, c'mere.
You listen to me and
you listen to me good.
No more call
s, no more nothing.
You see me, you
cross the street.
'Cause you'r
e a dangerous fuck
and i don't want
you in my life.
Don't go,
don't go!
I'll call your wife!
What'd you say?
I'll go to columbia,
i'll tell your
daughter about us.
C'mon!
C'mere, c'mere.
Now, you
listen to me...
you go near my
wife or my family
and i'll fuckin' kill
you, you understand me?
I'll fuckin'
kill you.
Go ahead,
kill me.
Kill me.
You fucking bitch!
Kill me,
kill me.
Kill me.
Kill me, kill me
, kill me, kill me...
kill me.
Kill me.
Alright,
this is it.
I don't care if god comes by,
you don't move this car.
When we go in,
you do the talking.
Me?
I know eugene, he'll
recognize my voice.
Don't worry
about it.
When they see this
motherfucker, nobody'l
l have to say a word.
What's the matter?
I don't know.
You sure you
wanna do this?
Why?
Don't you?
Fuck it, let's go
down the shore.
Let's do it
before the crank
wears off.
Ace,
high flush.
Flush talks.
Anybody
want a drink?
Nobody fuckin' move!
Just take it
easy, alright?
Shit.
Shut the fuck up!
Empty your pockets,
all of you!
C'mon!
Very bad, boys,
very bad.
This is a
low- level game, guys.
The only thing you're gonn
a get around here is practice.
You heard what he said,
shut the fuck up!
Take it ea
sy, take it easy!
You guys know who
you're robbin'?
Gimme your watch.
Remember the
old adage son.
Leave'em while
you're looking good.
Just give it to
him, sunshine.
Victory has
a hundred fathers
but defeat
is an orphan.
Shut up, shut up!
Stop fucking
looking at me!
Come on, hurry up!
Let's get the
fuck outta here!
If you can keep your head
while those around you can't--
where the
fuck is he?
Shit.
Shit, c'mon!
Get the fuck out!
Oh, my god!
Jackie!
Jackie,
jackie!
Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Hey, cocksucker.
Chris, please,
we didn't kn
ow you were in there.
We're with ralphie.
Please?
If you're one of
the thousands of men
who suffer from
erectile dysfunction,
you already know that
it's no laughing matter.
What you probably
don't know, however,
is that treatment is covered
by most medical plans--
dr. Frei
d, i'm sorry,
your service s
aid it was an emergency.
Hello?
Jesus christ.
Not again, tony.
I can't keep
doing this.
I'm in the middle of--
can't he go to
the emergency room?
I thought he
had a green card.
Manadgia la
putana fragita!
Will you s
hut the fuck up?
You're gonna m
ake him hit an artery.
Just try and relax, let
the sedative do its job.
You should thank
god they didn't
hit nothing important.
This fucking prick
is really a doctor?
Close, i'm a
prick doctor.
Get it?
While you're here
maybe he can give
you a bulge.
Doc, see if you
can remove this
ladies underwear.
Ah!
You're gon
na be alright.
That little
motherfucker.
He's goin', tony,
he's goin' big time.
You sure i
t was jackie jr.?
I find him, i'm
doing him tonight.
No, you're not.
Why not?
'Cause i saidso.
Why?
I don't gotta explain
anything to you.
Because he's
jackie aprile's kid?
You're not gonna
let this go, you
can't do that!
He took a shot at me,
he tried to kill furio!
We're made!
Every person you whack
, you risk exposure.
Major murder,
that's what the fe
ds ask for christmas.
Bullshit, you're a
fuckin' hypocrite.
What the f
uck did you say?
You preach all
this wiseguy shit
and meanwhile
the only ones who gotta
play by the rules are us!
I loved you!
What happens i
decide, not you.
You don't love me anymore,
well, that breaks my heart.
But it's too fuckin' bad
, 'cause don't gotta love me.
But you wi
ll respect me.
Ralph cifaretto's here.
What'd we say?
Ton'.
How you doing?
It's terrible, huh?
Ro's going nut
s over this.
She knows he hangs around
with this punk dino
and the other one.
Any word
from her son?
No.
Alright, c'mon.
This kid...
he did a
terrible thing.
Terrible.
Your fucking
card game.
I know how close
you are to the family.
I feel for you.
You're living
under the same roof.
And it was
my card game.
But, what
happened to sunshine,
it's a disgrace.
But, tell you
the truth, tony...
i wanna give
the kid a pass.
Yeah?
That's just me, though.
I know you got bigger
concerns, you're the boss.
I'll make sure
your orders are done,
whatever they maybe.
I think you should go with
your instincts on this, ralph.
You do?
But furio took a
hit and chris.
These are made men.
I'll make sure they
respect your decision.
'Cause i'm sure you're
gonna do the right thing.
That's why
i made you captain.
This is
rosalie's kid.
That's why i'll understand
if you wanna give him a pass
and i'm sure everybody
else will too.
And who cares
about shit they say
they don't have the balls
to say to your face?
The kid
disrespected you.
But they don't have to live
with your commitments.
And hey, your decision
goes the other way,
the one thing you
cannot do, ralph,
you cannot do,
is blame yourself.
You took this kid
under your wing.
You schooled him
as best you could.
Didn't you?
Jack spoiled him.
I think
this is yours.
Stupid kid was carrying it
around during the holidays.
She wanted me to
fucking kill her.
Like suicide by cop.
So, she
set me up?
From the beginning
gloria saw me
as only a
fuckin' hammer?
She loved you.
She looked so good, too,
that day in your office.
Just another irina
with a college degree.
Ask yourself.
How did you
recognize in gloria,
underneath all her
layers of sophistication,
this deeply wounded,
angry being
that would let you
replicate once again
your relationship
with your mother.
I don't want t
o fuck my mother.
I don't give a shit
what you say.
You're never
gonna convince me.
Not fuck.
Try to please her,
try to win
her love.
I'm 40 fuckin'
years old.
We need to repeat
what's familiar
even if it's
bad for us.
Gloria's need
for drama,
the selfishness,
the incessant
self regard.
At one time, in
your mother's hands,
it passed for love.
Alright, look,
you're her doctor,
you tell me,
do i gotta wor
ry about this broad?
She says she's gon
na tell carmela about us.
I honestly
can't predict.
But i think we
should deal with
why are you
so attracted
to dangerous
relationships?
Why do you put
your marriage in
such danger?
Maybe i'm lookin
g for a way out.
You ever
think of that?
Anthony,
you'll never
leave your wife.
Bullshit.
There's a limit
to how much shit--
she might leave you,
but you'll
never leave her.
Despite your mothering,
you made one good
decision in your life
vis- a- vis women,
you're not gonna
throw that over.
Your own selfishness is
too strong to let that happen.
Alright,
alright.
Actually,
in spite of everything,
you're a very
conventional man.
I said alright.
We have to
stop now.
Got pep, i'll
give it that.
Zero to 60, in under
seven seconds.
What's the matter,
you don't like me?
Look, i'm not back
in 10 minutes,
they call the cops.
Standard
operating procedure.
Here's some standard
Stay the fuck aw
ay from tony soprano.
Shut the fuck
up and listen.
It's over, capisce?
Over and done.
You call or go anywher
e near him or his family
and they'll be
scraping your nipples
off these fi
ne leather seats.
And here's the
point to remember,
my face is the last
one you'll see,
not tony's.
We understan
d each other?
It won't be
cinematic.
Any word,
anything?
He probably went
down to florida.
Ro, i'm sure
he's fine.
Ro, c'mon.
Sit down.
Look, um...
this is gonna be
hard for you to hear.
Oh, jesus christ!
It's okay,
it's just...
he's has a
very serious
drug problem.
What?
It's coke.
He may owe some
money to dealers,
something.
Oh, my god.
I didn't want to
tell you this.
Look, we're doing
everything we can.
Look, we're gonna
find him,
we'll get him help.
We'll get him
into rehab.
Let's just hope
he's not too far gone.
It smells good.
Lemon snaps for the
bake sale at church.
You look good.
I went to
step today.
Is that why you don't have any
of these looney- tune moods?
Exercise?
Where's your ring?
I had to bring it in
to get it sized,
it's a little big.
Hi, it's me.
I'll be home in
about 20 minutes.
Yeah, i picked u
p the stuffed shells.
No, the celantano's,
you just gotta heat'em up.
Captions copyright 2001
home box office
a division of time warner
entertainment company, L. P.